深入黑暗
第一季第一集
搞定了吗
Is it done?
他在吃撒丁蛆虫奶酪
He was eating Sardinian casu marzu.
我还以为国内
I didn't realize it was still possible
不可能买到蛆虫奶酪呢
to get casu marzu in this country.
一千多只蛆虫分泌的酸
The stomach acid of a thousand maggots
从内到外侵蚀了奶酪
rotting the cheese from the inside out,
让它价值更高
making it richer,
更滑口
smoother.
但是  为了要成功
But...for the whole thing to work,
你必须全部吃掉
you must eat all of it.
正是这些蛆虫才让它如此美味
The maggots are what make the experience wonderful.
我打来不是为了听
I didn't call you for
戈登·拉姆齐式评价的  威尔克斯
a Gordon Ramsay impression, Wilkes.
我再问一遍
I ask again.
搞定了吗
Is it done?
搞定了
It's done.
真想知道什么人会专门定蛆虫奶酪
I wonder what kind of a man gets casu marzu on demand.
你知道他是谁  对吗
You know who he is, don't you?
当然了
Of course I do.
媒体明天一大早会对他进行大肆报道
The press are breaking a story on him in the morning.
字幕
No one does this better than you,
必须得在明天变成那样之前把他送走
and I need him delivered before that happens.
凌晨两点之前把他带到老地方
Bring him to the usual place by 2am.
只剩四小时了
That's in four hours.
不得晚到
No delays.
我相信你一定会帮我办妥这件事的
I trust you to help me make a statement with this one.
他已经死了
Well, he's dead already.
剩余的应该不会花太久
The rest shouldn't take too long.
很好
Good.
威尔克斯
Oh, and Wilkes?
我知道你有你的风格  我尊重你
I know you have your own methods and I respect that.
但这次最好公事公办
But maybe try and treat this like business,
就这一次
just for once?
扮相真不错
Great costume.
尸体
西好莱坞
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
万圣节快乐  混蛋
Happy Halloween, dick!
翻译     小酸奶
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     紫夏  大葱  啾啾啾  小式
该死
God dammit!
这都是什么东西
What is this shit?
混蛋
Son of a bitch!
后期     8T
开玩笑吧
You've got to be kidding me!
总监     小酸奶
上帝啊
Holy shit, man!
看着点路
Watch where you're going.
搞什么
What the fuck?
上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
这是你做的吗
Did you make this?
真是难以置信
This is unbelievable.
天啊  哥们
Oh my God, dude.
看上去好逼真
This looks so real.
多多  你看看
Dot, look at this thing.
别叫我多多
Don't call me Dot.
等等
Wait a second.
你现在要去做什么
What are you doing right now?
我知道这么贸然问陌生人不好  但是
I know, I know that's a weird thing to ask a stranger, but, uh,
我们正要去一个派对
we're on our way to this party,
那里会非常非常酷
and it's gonna be outrageously cool
超级牛逼
and, like, super sick,
我本来想我们能搞个隆重登场
and I was kind of hoping we can make a big entrance
之类的  但是
at this thing, but, um,
如你所见
as you can see...
我们看上去很可悲  所以
we look pathetic, so...
我大概30分钟前刚下班吧  所以
I got off work, like, 30 minutes ago, so...
你还是能努力努力的  尼克
Still could have made an effort, Nick.
-我...  -你想扮成什么
- Well, I... - What are you supposed to be?
-你想扮成什么  -这是蒸汽朋克
- What are you dressed as? - This is steampunk.
-这和...  -护目镜
- This and... - Goggles?
你要打扮成护目镜吗
You're dressed as goggles?
抱歉  你是谁
I'm sorry, who are you?
该死  抱歉  艾伦·摩根·亚当斯
Oh, shit, sorry, Alan Morgan Adams
就是马萨诸塞州的那个摩根亚当斯[地名]
of the Massachusetts Morgan Adamses.
伙计
Hey, hey, buddy,
要去哪里呢
Where are we goin'?
你是
Are you, like, uh,
英国美国疯子之类的吗
the British American Psycho or something?
多萝西
Whoa, Dorothy.
抱歉  请原谅她
Sorry, you gotta forgive her.
她来自韦斯特莱克
She's from Westlake.
我们还在教她怎么礼貌待人
We're still workin' on her manners.
我们有点...
We're kind of a...
像《窈窕淑女》那一套
My Fair Lady type of deal.
他是那个自命不凡的醉鬼
He's the, uh, self-important drunk perv
觉得自己很了不起
who thinks that he's a big deal,
而我就是那个谁都想上的小太妹
and I'm just the bad ass everyone wants to hang out with.
这是你的...
So is this, like, your...
上一名被害人之类的吗
latest victim or something?
暂时算是
Yes, for now.
哥们  哥们  哥们
Okay, dude, dude, dude, dude.
你得跟我们来
Uh, you gotta come with us.
我要怎么说
What can I say
才能劝得动你
that is gonna get you there?
那里有个免费酒吧
There's gonna be an open bar.
你觉得怎么样
Does that do anything for you?
那里会有很多辣妞
There's gonna be outrageously hot chicks,
真的很辣
like crazy hot chicks.
-笑死我了  -好吧
- Fucking gag me. - Okay, okay.
所有人都会去哪里的  伙计
Everybody is gonna be there, man.
我保证
I can assure you
我们要去的这个派对
that the party we're going to
比你现在要去的
is a million times cooler
好上百万倍
than the party you were going to.
我哥们杰克
My buddy Jack,
他是主办的
he, uh, he's the host.
他经常
He always does this, like,
隆重登场
grand arrival,
大家都会吹他的打扮  但这个
and everyone flips out about his costume, but this thing,
这绝对让他望尘莫及
this is gonna blow his cock off.
听着  有人划破了我的轮胎
Look, uh, someone slashed my tires,
我真的需要...
and I really need...
你需要搭车
You need a ride.
没问题
Done.
我们能帮你
That we can do.
我们能载你一程  伙计
We can get you a ride, man.
没问题
Consider it done.
请你让开
Please walk away.
不  你...
Yeah, no, there's...
你不可能拖着这玩意
there's no way you're gonna get a cab
打到车的  哥们
with this thing, dude, so...
他说得对  很有道理  尼克
He's right, that's a good point, Nick.
谢谢你终于派上了点用场
Thank you for finally making a contribution.
没人会让你带着这东西
No one's gonna let you in the back of a cab
上出租车的  那会一团糟
with this thing, you'll make a mess.
跟我们去喝一杯
Come with us for one drink.
就一杯  你就能离开
Just one drink, you walk right back out,
回到大街上
you're out on the streets,
继续杀死你的受害者
you're killin' all your victims in no time.
你知道吗
You know what?
这主意听上去还真的不错
That actually sounds like a really good idea.
就这样吧
Let's do it.
什么
What?
真不敢相信这样就行了
I can't believe that worked.
我还真没想到
Wow, I did not see that coming.
这简直是我的巅峰之夜
It's the best night of my life.
真是太棒了
This is exciting.
多么棒的转折
What an exciting turn of events.
好好帮忙抬着  尼克
Lift with your legs, Nick.
我们有四个人呢
There's four of us.
如果我们能一起...
If we all just, um...
上帝啊
Oh my gosh.
刮轮胎的
Slashed your tires, huh?
这城里真是一群变态
Bunch of fuckin' savages in this town.
好好抬着  尼克
Put your back into it, Nick.
很重呢
It's pretty heavy.
我们到了
Oh yeah, here we go!
这边  这边  来
This way, this way, come on!
我们又来了
Here we go again!
绝对会很棒
That ought to be good.
把他放在那里
Prop him up there.
别动  好吗
Do not move, okay?
别动  我去找尼克
Don't move, I'm gonna go find Jack.
特别是这个
Especially this guy.
大家嗨起来
Everybody raise your hands!
这家伙去哪里了
Where is this guy?
帅哥美女们
Girls and boys,
还有变性的朋友们
queer gender friends,
请将你们的目光投向舞池中央
please turn your eyes to the dance floor
欢迎派对主人
and welcome your host,
杰克·贝克
Jack Baker,
怪兽制造者
Monster Maker!
该死
Oh, shit.
你好  艾伦
Hello Alan.
绝了
Unreal.
纯达尔摩  双倍
Dalmore neat, double.
给
Here.
给  要吗
Here, want it?
让一下
Excuse me.
你的装扮真是...
Your costume is...
天才
brilliant.
这不是装扮
It's not a costume.
更应该说是戏服吧
Uh, yeah, more of a prop, I guess, right?
这一套效果很棒
The whole package really works.
西装  血迹
The suit, the blood.
我叫玛姬
Maggie.
让他们吃蛋糕吧
Let them eat cake.
她没有这么说过
She never said that.
玛丽亚·安东尼特
You know, Marie Antoinette,
法国皇后  据传在提起穷人吃不饱饭时她说"让他们吃蛋糕吧"
她其实从来没有说过
she never actually said,
"让他们吃蛋糕吧"
"Let them eat cake."
这只是法国人用来
It was just a thing that French like to attribute
抹黑他们不喜欢的外来皇后的
to every foreign queen they didn't like the look of.
出了什么差错
I mean, when things go wrong,
明明能怪国王的贱皇后  为什么要怪国王呢
why blame the king when you can blame his bitch of a wife?
我觉得她是一名非常有内涵的女性
She's a very meaningful woman, I think.
非常著名
Um, famous,
也是对男性对女性偏见的一种讽刺
but as a caricature that confirms men's prejudices against women
轻浮  轻佻
frivolous, ditzy,
喜欢买鞋子
obsessed with buying shoes,
愚蠢  美丽  悲剧的小可怜
silly, pretty, tragic little bonbon
容易色情  容易藐视
good for porn, good for scorn,
别的就没了
nothing in between.
你对你的装扮还真是有很多想法
Well, you have really thought about your costume.
你拖着一具尸体到处跑也好意思说我
Says the guy dragging a corpse around?
你没有和什么朋友一起来吗  玛姬
Did you not come here with friends, Maggie?
我一个人
Just me.
我本来也在犹豫  但是今晚
I hesitated to come, but tonight felt like
总觉得冥冥之中会发生什么事
the kind of night something might happen.
你挑的衣服的确很不错
Well, you certainly make that costume work.
一个女孩子被邀请到这种派对时
A girl is expected to dress a little provocatively
就是约定俗成地要打扮得奔放一点
when she's invited to one of these parties.
为什么女孩子会想要
Why would a girl want to be
被邀请到这种派对
invited to one of these parties?
我不知道
Oh, I don't know,
这种派对
one of these parties,
这种俱乐部
one of these clubs,
这种工作
one of these jobs.
法国革命已经过去了230年了
It might be 230 years since the French Revolution,
但男孩子们还是想看到
but boys still need the illusion
愚蠢的悲剧的小可怜
of silly, tragic little bonbons.
也许那不是你的问题
Maybe that's not your problem.
也许我本来就很清楚这一点
Maybe that's obviously occurred to me before,
不需要一个陌生人来给我解释
and I don't need it mansplained to me by a stranger.
你花了多久塞东西进去的
So how long did it take you to stuff it?
不是塞的  更应该说是  卷起阿狸
You don't stuff it, it's more of, um...roll,
就像...用毯子包猪
like a...pig in blanket.
看起来应该很难卷好
Those are harder to roll cleanly than they look.
熟能生巧
It gets easier every time you do it.
我每年万圣节都会做一次
I do it this way every Halloween.
在普通的晚上抛尸
You have to be a lot more careful disposing of a dead body
得更小心
on a normal evening.
好吧
Right.
你想让我...
Would you like me to, uh...
给你科普一下吗
let you in on something?
人们总认为杀人是最难的
People think that killing is the hard part.
他们还认为下一步必须要做的是
They also assume that the necessary next step
隐藏证据
is hiding the evidence,
但其实不是
but it's not.
你隐藏不了  这不可靠
You can't do it, not reliably.
你得想点别的说法
You have to come up with an alternative story
编这个人的死因
for how this person died.
需要有专门的手法  专门的证据
Needs its own narrative, its own evidence,
专门的犯人
its own culprit.
需要花更大的力气
Takes more effort,
但如果你能处理得当
but if you can do it correctly,
就能成功
it works.
你什么都能做到
You can do anything,
只要你别给人足够的时间
as long as you don't give people the time to decide
发现其实和你告诉他们的有出入
it's something different from what you're telling them it is.
这就是为什么...这行
And that...is what makes this...
这么特殊
special.
有道理
That makes sense.
我也不确定你这装扮是不是这意思  不过
I'm not sure it all comes across in the costume, but...
有道理
that makes sense.
哥们  敬电影《黑色星期五》
Okay, dude, a toast to every Friday the 13th movie.
来吧
Let's do this.
《黑色星期五》
Friday the 13th.
《黑色星期五2》
Friday the 13th Part 2. Part 2.
"人生路过半
"Midway upon life's journey,
我发现自己在黑暗的森林中"
I found myself within a forest dark."
"面前的路通往迷途"
"For the straightforward path had been lost."
地狱空荡荡  恶魔在人间
Hell's empty and all the devils are here.
《黑色星期五8》
Jason Takes Manhattan.
你要走了吗
Are you leaving?
有人答应我要送我去工作
I've been promised a ride to work.
你跟那个叫艾伦的人一起来的吧
You came with that guy Alan, right?
他是杰克的工作
He's friends with Jack.
字幕
I work for Jack.
他在设计什么虚拟恐怖现实什么的
Um, he's designing this horror virtual reality thing,
我是干活的程序员
and I'm the coder who has to do all the damn work.
那些活...
It's really...
让你觉得你自己的学生贷款可真值
really makes you feel good about those student loan debts.
太值了
Worth it.
我可以
Um, I can, uh,
给你搞辆车  送你去
get you a car and drive you.
今晚有人在等你回家吗  玛姬
Is anybody expecting you home tonight, Maggie?
完全没有
Not a soul.
那好吧
Well, all right then.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你好啊  妹子
Hey, what's up, girl?
性骚扰是犯罪  混蛋
Hey, sexual harassment is a crime, shithead.
-随便了  -罪犯
- Whatever. - Criminal!
快准备好了
Uh, we're almost ready.
我只是...这尸体太重了
I just...the body thing is huge.
我只是...我们可能需要
I was just...figured we could use
找人帮忙抬下楼
some help getting it downstairs.
没有什么"我们"
There is no "We."
怎么了
What?
我只同意喝一杯  我都喝了三倍了
I agreed to one drink. I've had three.
车
Car, now.
-哥们  但丁  -别这样
- Dude, chill. - What, no.
我已经告诉玛姬你能借我的车了
I already told Maggie you can borrow my car.
淡定点
Now come on!
能不能放松点
Enjoy yourself for a bit, huh?
带我上你的车
Take me to your car now
不然我就在你的派对上把你杀了
or I will kill you at your own party.
你真的很像一个杀手
You really got this killer thing down.
你做得很棒
You nailed it.
我喜欢
I like it.
好吧  好吧
All right, all right.
我带你下楼
I'll take you downstairs.
但首先  抽几口
But first, shots!
终于有好东西了
Finally we get to the good shit.
哥们  他从来不放任何人进去的
Dude, he never lets anyone in there.
今天晚上绝对史无前例
This night's gonna be epic. Okay?
别弄坏什么东西了
Hey, don't break anything.
来吧  抽一点死不了
Come on, one shot won't kill you.
每一件
Every single one of those
都要好几千呢
literally cost thousands of dollars.
对  我有钱
Yeah, I got money
还有才
and talent.
我现在就需要车钥匙
So I'm gonna need those car keys now.
对  我们也许该回到派对上去了
Yeah, we should probably get back to the party.
别急  伙计们
Aw, not yet, guys.
来吧
Come on.
你到底这么急着去哪里
Hey, where are you going in such a hurry anyway?
我们能去吗
Can we come?
哥们
Yo, dude,
这是你的派对
this is your party.
萨沙·格雷是你的DJ
You got Sasha Grey DJing.
你不能离开...他不能离开排队
You can't leave...he can't leave the party.
我想干什么就干什么
I can do whatever I want.
伙计们  这就是今晚的重点
Guys, this...this is what tonight is all about.
万圣节前夕
All Hallow's Eve,
我们戴上面具
the night we put our masks on
放飞我们黑暗  未知的一面
and let our dark, unpredictable sides fly.
这家伙  伙计  看看他
This guy, man, look at him.
这装扮
The costume, woo!
这表演
The performance.
我告诉你  兄弟
I'm telling you, bro,
这简直上了一个档次
next level commitment.
伙计们  你们想想
Think about it, guys.
我们这一晚一般都是怎么结束的
How do we usually end the night?
我  坐在家里
Me, sittin' at home
看《外部空间》的《第九计划》
watching Plan 9 from Outer Space,
调鸡尾酒
mixing cocktails,
给多萝西轰炸屌照
sending unsolicited dick pics to Dorothy.
或者  伙计们  我们可以把派对继续下去
Or, guys, we keep the party goin', right?
把派对继续下去
Keep the party goin',
找个人
lookin' for somebody,
就像这位家伙
like this guy right here.
我不知道今晚是怎么回事
I don't know what's goin' down tonight,
但我感觉
but I am feeling so,
怎么说来着  很有活力
what's the word? Alive.
我感觉现在很有活力  伙计们
I'm feelin' so alive right now, guys.
他...
Yeah, he, um...
他偶尔
he occasionally, uh...
是会这样
does that.
等等
Wait.
等等  等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
还有动画效果
This animatronic too?
真是太棒了
Woo, that is amazing!
给他一脚  就会停下来了
Give it a kick, it'll stop.
你可以做得更好
You can do better than that.
真的吗
Oh, really?
好吧
All right.
该死
Shit!
我修好了吗
Did I fix it?
我不知道
I don't know.
修好了吗
Did you?
上帝啊
Jesus!
该死  那是一具真的尸体
Shit! That's an actual body!
那是一具真的尸体
That's an actual body.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay, okay.
那真的是一个死人
That's a dead person for real.
把你的手放下来
Put your fucking hands down.
抱歉
Sorry.
搭陌生人的车
Ugh, accepting a ride from strangers
总是一个糟糕的主意
is always such a bad idea.
那么
So, uh...
你杀了这个人吗
did you kill this guy?
他一分钟前还没死
Well, he wasn't dead a minute ago.
如果他现在死了  那严格来说
If he is now, then technically
是你杀了他
you killed him.
你  你是个杀手
Are you, uh, are you a hitman
之类的吗  还是...
or something, or...
上帝啊  伙计
Jesus Christ, man.
你不能就这么杀人
You can't just kill people!
当然可以
Course you can.
该死
Oh shit!
该死  伙计
Oh shit, man!
我才刚上了科技网《40名40以下成功人士》榜
I was just on VentureBeat's list of 40 under 40,
我不能就这么死了
I can't die like this!
好吧  你叫什么名字
Okay, what's your name?
杰克  对吧
It's Jack, right?
你是干什么的  杰克
And what do you do, Jack?
我是一名艺术家
Uh, I'm an artist.
我有信托基金  好吗
I have a trust fund, okay?
保妥
Please!
你觉得你自己是"理智"的吗
And would you define yourself as "Sane"?
我...我...
I...I...
你所做的除了
Anything you do other than
吃饭  睡觉  拉屎  做爱和杀戮以外的事
eat, sleep, shit, fuck, and kill
都是疯狂的标志
is a symptom of insanity.
在人类进化的
You see, there was a point
过程中
during human evolution where something,
出了一些神经上的分叉
some neuron pathway misfired,
我们自我的意识觉醒
and we all became self-ware.
也就是说  我们变得疯狂
That is to say, we became insane.
我们就是一团血肉
We are balls of flesh and bone
栖息在冰层上
on a rock of ice
在黑暗的宇宙中无序地转动
spinning through a dark, random universe
唯一的目的就是生存
designed only to survive,
但是然后我们基因中发生了某种变化
but then something happened in our DNA
我们想  "等等  等等
where we went, "Hey, wait, wait, wait.
万一我很重要呢
What if I matter?
万一这一切都是因为我呢"
What if it's all about me?"
你们有没有看过
Did you ever watch those, um...
大卫·爱丁保罗夫的节目
the David Attenborough shows?
BBC知名自然节目主持人
很棒吧
They're magnificent, right?
充满了死亡
Full of death.
但不知为何  看起来很合理
And yet in a way, it makes sense.
然后你看新闻  就觉得很疯狂
And then you try and watch the news and it's crazy.
完全没有道理
There's no sense at all.
然后我还有另一个问题的答案
And I will answer that other question for you.
疯了的人知道自己疯了吗
Does a crazy person know they're crazy?
知道  这叫良知
Yes, it's called a conscience.
吉姆尼·克里克特
Jiminy Cricket,
那只是我们的大脑
that's just the part of our brains
因为被分裂成我们的本我和
screaming at the psychic tear
我们所假装成的样子
caused by the gulf between what we are
而在泪水中发出的尖叫
and what we pretend to be.
你觉得世界需要你的涂鸦吗  艺术家
You think the world needs your doodles, artist?
自然界中没有艺术
There's no art in the natural world.
只有谋杀
There is murder.
你真的觉得
Do you really think
他生或死对自然界来说
it made a difference to the world
有什么区别吗
if he lived or died?
这简直是我挺过最动听的话
That was the most amazing thing i've ever heard.
你知道我有多
Do you know how often
经常想要这么做吗
I've wanted to do that to somebody?
那真是...
That's a...
车钥匙  快点
Car keys, now.
杰克  他会把我们都杀了
Jack, he's gonna fucking kill us.
他说得对
He is right.
不管怎样  如果你答应帮我
However, if you agree to help me,
我保证会赶紧完事
I promise I'll make it quick.
最上面的抽屉
Top drawer.
你
You.
关上抽屉
Close the drawer.
那是怎么回事
What the hell was that?
我改装成用来逃生的
I rigged it as an escape route.
我本来想靠这个泡妹子
I thought it would be a fun way to impress girls.
真是太逊了
That is so rapey.
天啊
Oh my God!
走走走
Go, go, go, go.
-杰克  杰克  你...  -杰克
- Jack, Jack, what are you - Jack!
停  停下音乐
Stop, stop the music!
拜托快报警
Please, somebody call the police!
有一名客人要杀了我们
One of my guests is trying to kill us!
搞什么
What the fuck?
快走
Come on!
上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
快走  快走
Go, go, go.
我不知道抽屉的事  我发誓
I didn't know about the drawer, I swear.
你怎么回事
What's wrong with you?
我了解杰克
I know Jack.
如果有捷径能离开这个房间
If there's a shortcut way out of this room,
肯定能通过某些低劣  下流
it's gonna be revealed by some smug, nerdy
无聊的机关找到
inside joke onanism.
我能找出来
I can figure it out.
谢谢你
Thank you.
快点  快点
Hurry up, come on!
伙计们  我们在干什么
Guys, what the hell are we doing, huh?
我们为什么要带走这玩意
But why did we take this thing?
哥们  这玩意是个人
Dude, this thing is a person.
哥们  举报这家伙可能有奖赏
Dude, there's probably a reward out on this guy.
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?
举报一名杀人犯总是会有奖赏的
There's always a reward when you turn in a murderer.
他们会给我们一笔钱
They're gonna give us a pile of money.
人人都会爱我们
Everyone's gonna love us.
我们就会成为英雄
We're gonna be heroes!
天啊  你是什么东西啊
Oh my, what are you,
赏金猎人狗吗
Dog the Bounty Hunter?
你不是因为这个才一起搬这玩意的吗
Is that not why you picked it up?
这不是"玩意"
Uh, it is not an it,
这是一个人
it is a person
可能还活着
that might still be alive.
好吧  但那个人可能想把他要回去
Yeah, but that guy's gonna want him - back.
等等
Wait.
这为什么突然变成我们的问题了
Why is this suddenly our problem?
好吧
Okay.
我们要把他交给警察
We're gonna give him to the cops
然后他就和我们没关系了  好吗
and then he stops being our problem. Okay?
杰克  钥匙呢
Jack, keys?
什么
What?
你本来要载那家伙一程的
You were giving that guy a ride.
是啊  但是他疯了
Yeah, but he went all psycho
我都没来得及拿钥匙
before I could grab the keys.
那我们为什么要下来这里
Then why the fuck are we down here?
我以为你们开车来的
I thought you guys drove!
天啊
Oh my God!
尼克开车载我们来的  混蛋
Nick drove us, you jackass.
他停在三个街区外了
He parked three blocks away.
那他的钥匙在哪里
Okay, so where are his keys?
该死
Aw, shit.
他对你的揣测没错  对吗
He wasn't wrong about you, was he?
你的确是个杀手
You are a hitman, right?
我们可是可能在这里关上很久的
Could be in here for a really long time, you know?
-哥们  优步  -对
- Dude, Uber, right? - Yes.
-没错  -你在开玩笑吗
- Yes. - Are you kidding me?
报警
Call 911.
好吧
Okay, uh...
该死  我把手机丢在楼上了
Shit, I left my phone upstairs.
天啊  好吧
Oh my God, okay, fine.
我来轿车
I'll get the car.
没有人会让我们
No one is gonna let us
带着尸体上车的
get into the car with a body.
不  他们能和我们一起当英雄
No, no, they can be heroes with us.
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
报警
Look, call the cops.
等等  等等
Uh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
我们来的时候
When we came in here,
外面就有警察
there were cops outside.
对  去  快去
Uh, yes, uh, go, go now.
快去
Go.
你说你想要什么来着  兰迪
What did you say you wanted, Randy?
肉桂葡萄干百吉饼  半黄油  半
A cinnamon raisin bagel, toasted, half butter--half
不然会滴下来
otherwise it gets all drippy.
咖啡加两份奶  两份糖
Two creams, two sugars in the coffee.
这是怎么回事
Oh, what the hell is this?
调度中心  这里是1A78小队
Central, this is Unit 1-Alpha-7-8.
我这应该又有一个酒后闹事的
Think I got another drunk and disorderly.
他可能是吸毒了
He's possibly on drugs.
-拜托  -绝对嗑药了
- Please! - Definitely on drugs.
拜托  我需要你
Please, I need you.
你在干什么
Hey, what the hell are you doin'?
天啊  见到你真是太好了
Jesus Christ, I'm so happy to see you.
离车窗远一点
Step back from the window.
快点
Now.
长官
Sir, um,
我的朋友们都在那边
my friends, they're down there,
都在那边的楼里
and in the building over there.
我们  我们需要你跟我来
We--we need--we need you to come.
我需要你跟我来  拜托
I need you to come with me, please.
威斯特  我这里有几个醉鬼
Hey West, I got a couple of drunks to deal with.
要我回来吗
You need me to come back?
不用  我可以的
Nah, I got it.
好吧  孩子
All right, son.
带我去吧
Show me.
快点快点快点
Come on, come on, come on!
拜托快点
Please hurry up, come on!
他要回来了
He's coming back!
好吧
Okay.
不
No...
《基督山伯爵》
Count of Monte Cristo.
经典越狱用具
Classic prison escape scene.
密码很可能是《驱魔人》
Code is probably the release date
或者《五百年后》的发行日期
for The Exorcist or THX1138 or...
我们合作得很愉快啊
We work pretty well together.
没有什么"我们"
There is no "We."
伙计们
Guys!
-太好了  -太好了  太好了
- Oh, yes! - Yes, yes, yes!
太好了
Yes!
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
拜托  伙计们
Come on, guys.
我知道现在是万圣节
Look, I know it's Halloween and everything,
但是这玩意还是能
but you could really scare the hell
把人吓出老命
out of somebody with this thing.
不不不  拜托  我们需要你的帮助
Oh, no, no, please, uh, we need your help.
别过来  女士
Stay where you are, miss.
警官  拜托
Uh, officer, please
别过来
Hey, stay where you are!
不不不  拜托
No, no, no, please,
你不明白
you don't understand.
指挥部  有人袭警
Command, I got a code 6A,
三名吸毒者  一名精神崩溃的女性
three intoxicated persons, one hysterical female.
你这个混蛋
You fucking asshole!
后退
Stand down!
女性可能持有武器
Female is possibly armed.
后退什么  你这个白痴
Stand down from what, you fucking moron?
有人死了
Someone is dead here
我们需要你的帮助
and we need your help.
好了  好了
Whoa, whoa, whoa, okay, okay.
越扯越远了
It's gettin' away from us here.
我知道这看上去不大妙
I know this doesn't look good.
听我说  我叫艾伦·摩根·亚当斯
Just listen to me. My name is Alan Morgan Adams.
马萨诸塞州的那个摩根亚当斯
Of the Massachusetts Morgan Adamses.
你要抓的不是我们
Okay, uh, we are not the ones you're looking for.
他马上就会到这里来
He is going to be here any fucking second,
不  不许动
No, freeze right now!
不  等等
No, wait!
看  这是个真人
Look, it's a real person.
等等  这是我以为的那个人吗
Wait, is that who I think it is?
他很有名
He's famous.
还很有钱
And rich.
还很漂亮
And beautiful.
好吧  等等  再跟我
All right, so wait, just walk
跟我说一遍是怎么回事
walk me through all this again.
不  你得赶紧呼叫增援
No, no, you need to call for backup right now
不然我们都得死
or we are all going to die.
告诉我是谁干的
You tell me who did this.
伙计们
Guys.
是他干的
He did it.
你给我站住
Hey you, stop right there!
-该死  -不许动
- Oh, shit. - Freeze!
开枪打那个混蛋
Just shoot the bastard!
小姐  后退
Miss, you stay back,
交给我来处理
you let me take care of this.
这是给你的最后一次警告
Now this is your last warning.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你觉得这位威格姆队长[动画人物]
Do you really think Chief Wiggum's
能拯救世界吗
gonna save the day?
说得好
Good point.
把手举到我看得到的地方
Put your hands where I can see them.
我说举起手来
I said put your hands up!
等等
Ooh, wait.
天啊
Oh God...
站住
Hey, stop!
喂  站住
Come on, stop!
别跑
Don't go anywhere!
你们给我站住
You stop right now!
搞什么
What the hell!
我...
I...
兰迪
Hey Randy.
没有肉桂葡萄干百吉饼  哥们
They're out of cinnamon raisin, buddy.
你敢信吗
Can you believe that?
你是杀人犯  他们是小偷
You're a murderer, they're thieves,
结果中枪的是我
I'm the one who gets shot.
好吧  我能找到他们
Okay, I can find them.
我只需要一台电脑
I just need a computer.
如果他们有手机
If they have a cell phone,
我就能追踪他们
I can track them.
新鲜的伤口
A flesh wound.
边走边说
Talk and walk.
伙计们  我们现在要怎么办
Guys, what the fuck are we gonna do now?
天啊  我从来没有
Oh my God, I've never been
这么接近过名人
this close to a famous person before.
哥们  放下
Dude, put that thing down, man!
不  我们不放
No, we're not putting him down!
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
你们都知道他是谁
You guys know who this is
我们可是拯救他的人
and we get to be the ones that rescued him.
等等
Wait a second.
你知道吗
Hey, you know what?
我们不能救他
We're not rescuing him
因为他死了
because he's dead!
好吧  随便吧
Okay, whatever.
我们不能走大路
We need to get off the street, okay?
他为什么不杀
And why couldn't he just kill,
伊利亚·伍德之类名气小点的人呢
like, Elijah Wood or someone small?
我们可以推走这个
We could just take that.
对  你想抢一个流浪汉吗
Yeah, you want to rip off a homeless guy?
你要不要顺便
Do you want to shoot a puppy
弄死一只小狗
while we're at it too, hmm?
抱歉  难道你更希望
Oh, I'm sorry, would you rather
那个该死的疯子追上我们吗  多多
that the fucking psychopath catches up with us, Dot?
-好吧  好吧  -没错
- Okay, okay. - That's right.
-嗯嗯嗯  -谢谢
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - Thank you.
好吧好吧
Yep, right, right, right.
我们想借一下这个
Hi, we just need to borrow this.
除非从我...
Over my dead...
尸体上跨过
body.
对  那就是尸体
Yeah, that, that exactly, yes, um...
这样就行了吧
Uh, that's good enough, right?
对
Yup.
抱歉  我们会妥善使用的
So sorry, we're gonna take really good care of it.
非常感谢
Thanks so much.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
我知道流浪汉问题非常复杂
Hey, I know homelessness is a complex issue
不能仅仅靠慈善机构
that can't be solved by charity alone,
所以我希望这能帮你改善一下情况
so I, uh, I hope this helps the situation just a little.
抱歉  伙计
Sorry, man.
谢谢
Thank you.
上帝保佑你
God bless you.
杰克  走了
Jack, come on!
收到一则新信息
你要迟到了吗
不会迟到  两点如约
你很冷静
You're very calm
虽然刚刚丢失了
for someone who's just lost
自己杀人的证据
the bodily evidence that he's a murderer.
对  跟我说说怎么会丢的
Yes, remind me how that happened again.
这可能会有用
This might come in handy.
根据你说得
Just doing what you said.
新的证据  新的犯人
New evidence, new culprits,
新的手法  对吧
new narrative, right?
你能...
Could you...
你能脱掉这身连体衣吗
could you just take that jumpsuit off?
-等等  在这里吗  -没错
- Wait, what, out here? - Yes, yes.
我们需要找人帮忙  伙计们
We need somebody to help us, you guys.
我们要格外小心  好吗
We're trying to be discreet, okay,
他在一英里外就能看到你这身衣服  所以...
and he can see you from a mile off with that, so...
我底下可能什么都没穿的
I could be naked under this.
这算格外小心吗
Is that discreet?
哥们
Hey, dude,
你为什么现在给我发信息
why are you texting me right now?
我没有  我连手机都没带
I'm not, I don't have my phone.
那怎么...
Then what's...
不
Oh no.
艾伦
Alan?
杰克
我杀了他们  你把他们藏起来  说好了  对吧
等等  是那个警察吗
Wait, is that the cop?
该死
Oh shit.
哥们  你的手机在他手上
Dude, he has your fucking phone.
这不大妙  对吧
That's bad, right?
等等  我不明白  为什么...
Wait, I don't get it, why is...
我不知道
I--I don't know,
但我感觉这不是好事
but I feel like that can't be good.
这还有  表情
There's, like, emojis.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
他在陷害我们  拜托
He is framing us, hello!
操
Fuck!
-操  操  -该死
- Fuck, fuck! - Shit!
他就是想这么挫
That's exactly what he's doing.
操
Fuck me!
天啊  天啊
Oh God, oh my God.
开什么玩笑
Fucking be kidding me.
真操蛋
Fuck my life, shit!
Fuck that shit, man!
不可能是这样的
Okay, this can't be happening right now.
他不知道我们在哪里  对吧
He doesn't know where we are.
-没错  -对吧
- That's true. - Right?
好主意
That's a good point.
我们可以直接扔掉这个死人
We can ditch the dead guy
然后就此分道扬镳
and just go our separate ways.
我们可以随便丢在哪里
We can leave it anywhere.
不  那不是什么好主意
No, that is not a good idea.
他杀了尼克  你还踩了这个家伙的头
He killed Nick, and you stomped on this fucking guy's head.
这个疯子
I am not the one
可不是我请到我家的
who fuckin' brought that lunatic into my house.
好吧  那套装扮真是太棒了
Okay, that costume was amazing.
-那不是装扮  -那不是装扮
- It wasn't a costume! - It wasn't a costume!
天啊  天啊  这是万圣节
Oh my God, oh my God, it was Halloween!
我怎么知道
How was I supposed to know?
哥们  哥们  哥们
Dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude.
那个死掉的警察
Okay, that dead cop
记了我的名字  伙计
took my name, man.
他用无线电汇报了我们
He radioed in about us.
你知道为什么吗
You know why?
因为你天天到处丢你的名字
Because you're always throwing your name around.
看  你丢了点东西
Oh, look, you dropped something.
是你的名字
Your fuckin' name.
对  变成我的错了
Oh, yeah, that's my fault.
都怪我  好吧
That's on me, okay.
没错
Oh yeah, it is.
你知道吗
You know what?
祝你好运
Good luck with it.
我受够了
I'm fuckin' done.
-我不干了  -你不干了
- I'm out. - You're done?
你要走吗
Oh, you're gonna go?
你准备就这么离开吗
You're gonna walk away from here?
你的主意还真是不错
Oh, this is really something coming from you.
顺便  快问快答
Hey, by the way, quick question.
你这辈子第一次遇到
How you doin' with the very first problem
不能用钱解决的问题
in your entire life
感觉怎么样
that you couldn't just throw money at, huh?
How's that goin' for you?
你在抽我毒品时
You didn't mind my money
对我的钱可没有意见
when you were hooverin' up my fuckin' drugs, right?
没错
Oh yeah,
你还给我推荐
and you were pitchin' me
你那个愚蠢的应用
your stupid fuckin' apps.
我愚蠢的应用
My stupid fucking apps?
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up,
你们俩都一样  天啊
both of you, oh my God!
尼克  尼克死在你的工作室
Nick, Nick is dead in your studio.
警察  死在你的车库
The cop, dead in your garage.
你们俩的手机上都有照片
There's photos on both of your phones.
好吧  也许如果
All right, maybe if...
也许如果我们把尸体还回去
maybe if we just give the body back,
我去道个歉
and I'll say sorry.
醒醒
Oh, wake up!
我们对那家伙一点都不了解
We know nothing about this guy.
他知道我们的名字  你的地址
He has our names, your address.
我是说  艾伦几乎给了他他的简历
I mean, Alan gave him his fucking résumé.
我们不需要一直互相揭短吧  伙计们
Okay, we don't need to keep putting each other down, you guys.
那个疯子戴着手套
Okay, that psycho, he wore gloves.
上面全是我们的指纹
Our prints are all over it.
不管我们手上
He's gonna kill us
有没有这玩意  他都会杀了我们
whether or not we have this thing.
这是一个人
It's a person.
别说废话了  好吗
Fuck all that noise, okay?
警察  等警察来找我们
And the cops, when the cops come looking for us,
他们会朝我开枪
they're gonna shoot me,
然后他会把你们全关起来
and then he's gonna lock you both up.
你们想冒这个险吗
Do you want to risk that,
你们想这么做吗
is that what you want to do?
我们该怎么办
What the fuck do we do?
我们把它处理掉
We make it go away.
没有尸体  就没有证据
No body, no evidence.
我们要用漂白剂
We gotta bleach him.
磨掉他的牙齿
Pulverize the teeth.
烧掉指纹
Burn off the fingerprints.
毁掉他的脸
We disfigure the face.
把他融了
We melt him down.
放干血和体液
We drain the blood and the bodily fluids.
和漂白剂混在一起
We mix those with bleach.
体内也要使用漂白剂
We also bleach the inside.
把他切成很小的块块
We chop him into pieces small enough
这样就算有人找到了部分残渣
that they can't be recognized as human
也根本认不出这是人
in case somebody finds one of 'em.
用醋酸软化骨头
Vinegar to soften the bones.
用不同的塑料袋分装各个部位
We put each part in a different plastic bag,
用碱液装满  系紧  然后每袋都
fill 'em with lye, tie the tops, and we bury them
埋得越远越好
as far away from each other as possible.
所以你才单身
Uh, that is why you're single.
好吧
Oh, okay.
只有我一个人看过《绝命毒师》吗
I'm the only one of us that watched Breaking Bad?
你们在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
那部剧简直是重新定义了"电视剧"
That show redefined television.
好吧
Okay, uh...
我们要去哪儿干这些事
where exactly are we meant to do all this?
我不知道  但你知道吗
I don't know, but you know what?
反正不在这里  所以我们...我们走吧
Not here, so let's...let's just go.
走吧
Let's go, yeah.
行吧  不  那我来推吧
Oh, okay, no, I'll get it.
谢了  多谢你们的帮助
Thanks, guys, thanks for all of your help.
非常感激
Appreciate it.
你们这些蠢蛋
You dumb dicks.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
你为什么会有枪
Why do you have a gun?
为什么没有
Why wouldn't I?
万一我去看电影
What if I go to the movies
或者进行节育
or my local Planned Parenthood
然后冲进来一个拿枪的混蛋开始扫射呢
and some asshole comes in with a gun to shoot everyone?
要是人人都带钱
Nobody would've gotten hurt tonight
今晚根本不会有人受伤
if everybody had a gun.
我会工作到很晚
I work long hours,
清晨去跑步
I go running early.
这让我更有安全感
It makes me feel safer.
你曾经被迫用过吗
Have you ever had to use it?
我刚刚在你面前杀了两个人
I just killed two people right in front of you.
我知道  下一个是谁
I know, who's gonna be next?
你没有理解我说的话的含义
You're not grasping the reality of what I'm saying.
我杀人
I kill people.
你还没杀我
You haven't killed me.
走吧
Come on.
先把你身上弄干净
Let's get you cleaned up.
*没人知道我是谁*
*No one knows who I am*
*没人认出我*
*Nobody recognizes me*
*没人知道我该是谁*
*No one knows who I'm supposed to be*
*万圣节*
*For Halloween*
纯达尔摩  以及一杯略浓的
Dalmore neat, and a slightly burnt, perfect,
斯皮史密斯和科基马蒂尼
Sipsmith and Cokey martini,
用扭吸管和
straight up with a twist,
12年的原桶威士忌
12 year Coal Ila for the scotch.
怎么了
What?
点酒不该超过25个字
A drink order shouldn't have 25 words in it.
看那两个人
Look at these two.
稍等一下
Hold that for a sec.
我得先去...
Uh, I'm gonna go...
处理一下
take care of this.
回来后去那个卡座
That booth when you get back.
*今年的万圣节*
*This year for Halloween*
*我只想做我自己*
*I'll just be me*
谢谢
Thank you.
吞屌就给你钱
待在学校吧
玛姬  你在做什么
Maggie, what are you doing?
这太疯狂了吧
Is this crazy?
不
No.
这种人不是随便就能碰到的
You don't meet guys like this every day.
他很聪明  他很强大
He's...he's smart, he's strong,
他受雇的
he's employed.
他能驾驭你
He can handle you.
时机有点不对  不过没关系
Timing's a bit off, but that's okay.
通过冲突成长
Grow through conflict.
你割我砍
五金和电锯
到了
Yeah, yeah, this is it.
那现在怎么办
All right, what now?
锁很破了
Uh, well, padlock is shit,
我们需要里面的东西  所以
and we need what's in there, so.
这辈子骑的自行车都没花过钱
Never paid for a bike in my life.
好吧  来吧
Okay, let's do this.
这一切好像并不在你计划之内
So this doesn't feel like much of a plan.
你说你能用电脑追踪到他
You said you could track him with a computer.
你能黑进这台吗
Can you get into this?
我是数据工程师  不是黑客
I'm a data engineer, not a hacker.
可以
Yes.
给我点时间绕过这家伙的密码
Just take me a minute to get around this guy's password.
我会为你找到这些混蛋
I'm gonna find those assholes for you.
什么
What?
全拿齐了吗
Is this everything?
到时候就知道了
I guess we're about to find out.
认真的吗
Seriously?
别再挑我毛病了  多萝西
Don't deny me this, Dorothy.
今晚已经超出我的想象了
Tonight isn't really what I was expecting, okay?
所以没错
So, yeah,
我要一把大砍刀
I want a machete.
好吧
All right.
剧里说应该从脸开始
It says we start with the face.
我还是不敢相信就是他
I still can't believe it's him.
我知道
I know.
他在推特上不是有两千万粉丝吗
Doesn't he have like 20 million Twitter followers?
现在没了
Not anymore.
好吧
Okay.
我进去了
I'm in.
你现在可以追踪任何人的智能手机了
You can track pretty much anybody's smartphone
只要他们手机的后台
as long as a single one of their apps
有运行一个程序
has live location in the background.
代码在跑了
Code's running.
我不得不说
So I gotta say,
看到你做事
seeing you do what you do,
听你说话
hearing you talk.
突然一切感觉都说得通了
Suddenly so much makes sense.
为什么
How?
你回答我一个问题
I'll answer one of yours
我就也回答你一个问题
for each one you answer of mine.
来嘛
Come on.
所有的秘密和欺骗
All the secrets, the deceptions.
你肯定很想找人说说心里话吧
You must be dying to just talk straight to someone.
你为什么要来这里
Why are you here?
因为我想来
Because I wanna be.
为什么
Why?
轮到我了
My turn.
谁雇的你
Who paid you?
我不知道
I don't know.
我从来没见过他
I never meet him.
你知道暗网是什么吗
Do you know what the dark web is?
知道
Yes.
加密不可追踪的网络
The part of the internet that's encrypted and untraceable...
想杀人的话就上那个网
where you would go if you want someone killed.
的确是可供选择的平台之一  没错
It's one of the many places you can go to do that, yes.
我们肉眼可见的世界过于光明美好
The visible world is so bright and reassuring,
但总是需要黑暗的
but it needs the dark.
雇我的人拥有黑暗
The man who pays me owns the dark.
你不认识他  他不认识你
You don't know him, he doesn't know you.
他用电子货币付款
You get paid in electronic currency.
完全匿名
Completely anonymous.
你杀死袋子里的人能得到多少酬劳
How much did you get for the guy in the bag?
比任何目标  都多
More than anyone, ever.
我还以为你只是长得帅
And I thought you were hot
没想到还很有钱
before I knew you were rich.
轮到你了
Your turn.
你知道我为什么喜欢万圣节吗  玛姬
Do you know why I like Halloween, Maggie?
糖果
The candy?
人类
People.
他们这辈子都戴着面具
They wear masks their whole lives,
假装生命有意义
pretending that life has meaning.
当你设了人
When you kill somebody,
这一切都会化为泡影
all of that's gone.
万圣节是人类最接近于承认
Halloween is the closest people come to admitting
我们由死亡定义的时刻
that we are defined by death.
你怎么会做这一行
How do you come to do what you do?
选了自己喜爱的职业
Choose a job you love,
下辈子都不用工作了
you never have to work a day in your life.
我也想拥有这个选择
I want that choice.
人总是生不由己
Life carries most people along.
很多事
So much happens,
根本没有意义
so little is made to happen.
但人生都是有后果的
But life is consequence.
你丢下一个玻璃杯  杯子会碎
You throw a glass, it breaks.
你划伤别人  他们会流血
You cut someone, they bleed.
你杀人  他们就死了
You kill someone, they're gone.
我总是被教导要敬畏后果
I was always taught that consequences are to be feared.
我做的每个决定
Every decision I make,
我生命中的每一刻
every second of my life
都是基于别人想要什么  需要什么
is based on what someone else wants or needs,
就像一团垃圾
it's like a fucking straitjacket.
然后你出现了
And then there's you,
你说后果只是权力的证明
saying consequences are proof of power.
你想做什么都行
You can do anything you want.
放手去做
All of it's good, do it.
因为一切都没有意义
Because none of it means anything.
第一次
Was it hard
杀人难吗
to kill someone the first time?
玛姬
Maggie...
什么都不难
None of it's hard.
死警察对交易可不利
Dead cops aren't good for business.
找到他们
Find them.
出了点状况
There was a complication.
小状况
Small.
所以呢
So?
所以没什么
So nothing.
一切都在我掌控中
I've got it under control.
这不像你  威尔克斯
This isn't like you, Wilkes.
十几年来第一晚出点状况
One complicated night in a decade
不能算坏记录
isn't a bad track record.
我希望你知道我的尸体在哪里
I hope you know where my body is.
你在监视我
You're watching me.
也许
Maybe.
偶尔吧
On and off.
协议中可没写这一条
That wasn't part of the deal.
也没写你可以向我撒谎
Neither is lying to me.
大白鲨也有天敌  威尔克斯
Even great white sharks have their predators, Wilkes.
两小时
Two hours.
解决你的麻烦
Sort your mess out.
别让我失望
Don't let me down.
操
Fuck me!
别喷你的脸  杰克
Don't touch your face, Jack.
那几乎是纯酸
It's basically acid.
好的
Okay.
接下来呢
What's next?
烧掉他的指纹
Burn off his fingerprints.
你  轮到你了
You, it's your turn.
快点
Now.
好吧
Okay.
该死
Oh, shit.
皮肤掉下来了
The skin is coming off!
-天啊  -操
- Oh, God. - Fuck, ahh!
好吧
Okay, ahh!
操
Oh, fuck.
他渗水了
He's leaking.
他渗水了  他渗水了  好吧
He's leaking, he's leaking. Okay.
天啊  天啊
Oh, God. Oh, God.
为什么艾伦不用干这种恶心的活
Why isn't Alan doing any of this gross shit, huh?
明明是他给我们捅的篓子
He's the one that got us into this mess.
总得有人
Hey! One of us has to keep our eye
掌控全局
on the bigger picture, okay?
我负责看步骤
I will look up the instructions,
你们俩负责实施
and you two carry them out.
谢谢
Thank you.
快点
Chop, chop.
我们得赶紧找到那具尸体
We need to find that body, now.
你说"我们"
You said "We."
好了  找到他们了
Okay, this is them.
他们在十个街区外的五金店
They're at a hardware store 10 blocks from here.
艾伦在搜索
Alan is doing a Google search.
看起来他好像是想
Trying to destroy a body,
毁掉一具尸体
by the looks of it.
现在我可以进入那个区域内任何
Now I can tap into any camera in the area
有内置传感器或驱动的摄像头
with a built-in sensor or actuator.
找到他们了
There they are.
这是实时的吗
Is this live?
这是十分钟前
It was 10 minutes ago.
如果我用"找到我的朋友"联接艾伦和杰克
If I connect Alan and Jack using Find My Friends,
我们就能用杰克的手机找到他们
we can track them with Jack's phone.
随身摄像头录像会实时上传到云服务器
Body cam footage is instantly uploaded to a cloud server.
你能连接到服务器吗
Can you access that server?
那这台电脑也能被追踪到
It'll be traceable to this computer.
我不介意
I'm okay with that.
我也是
Me too.
找到有我们的录像并删除
Find the video we're in and delete it.
我们应该发给他们
We should send it to them.
我们已经把照片发过去了
We've already sent the photos.
来找点乐子吧
Let's have a little fun.
警官
Hey, Officer.
不给糖就捣蛋  混蛋
Trick or treat, motherfucker.
你们好啊  伙计
Yeah, what's up, boy?
你们看上去棒极了
You guys look great.
敦德·米福必胜
Dunder Mifflin for the win!
该死
Oh, shit.
该死  过来
Oh, shit, get over here.
伙计们
Guys.
听着  我们有一具尸体
Look, we have a dead body here.
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help.
有人死了
Someone has been murdered.
好吧  越扯越远了
Okay, okay, it's gettin' away from us here.
我知道这看上去不大妙  警官
This isn't what it looks like, Officer.
听我说  我叫艾伦·摩根·亚当斯
Just listen to me, my name is Alan Morgan Adams.
这家伙到底什么毛病
What is this guy's problem?
天啊
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
天啊  天啊
Oh, my God, oh my God.
-我们怎么办  -冷静  冷静
- What do we do? - Focus, focus, focus.
不  我们怎么办  我们怎么办
No, what do we do, what do we do?
没有我们杀死那警察的证据
There is no footage of us killing the cop
因为不是我们干的
because we didn't actually do it.
他只是想吓唬我们
He's just trying to freak us out.
他想让我们崩溃
He's trying to make us crack,
这就是他的把戏
that is all he's doing.
-天啊  -成功了
- Oh, my God. - Yeah, well, it's working.
我崩溃了
I'm cracked.
艾伦  我需要你连接到杰克的苹果账号
Alan, I need you to log on to Jack's Apple account,
找到我的手机
Find My iPhone,
然后删除所有的信息
and then delete all the messages.
就这样
That's it.
等等  我要怎么做到这些事
Wait, how do I do any of that?
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
那你来  杰克
You do it then, Jack!
-我不知道怎么做  -没错
- I don't know how! - Exactly!
这些事我都是雇书呆帮我做的
I pay nerds to do that for me.
好吗
All right?
玛姬
Maggie.
玛姬在协助他
Maggie's helping him.
等等  今晚和他一起的金发女郎吗
Oh, wait, the blonde that was with him tonight?
对  就是那个穿得像
Yeah, the one that was dressed as, um...
《冰雪女王》里的艾尔莎一样
uh, Elsa from Frozen.
法国艳后  你这个白痴
Marie Antoinette, you dipshit!
你脑子里面除了有动画片
Do you know anything about anything
还能有点别的东西吗
that's not been made into an action figure?
很抱歉  教授
I'm so sorry, professor.
我不是文明战争历史的专家
I'm not an expert in Civil War history, okay?
等等  等等
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait,
等等  伙计们  这上面说
hold on, you guys, it says here
碱液需要作用好几个小时
the lye is gonna take like hours to work.
该死  我们得加热到
Oh, shit. We have to heat it
将近1000度
to almost a thousand degrees?
你不会在我们开始之前告诉我们吗
You didn't think to tell us that before we started?
你自己不会看吗  多多
You could've looked it up your fucking self, Dot!
再叫我多多试试
Call me Dot one more fucking time.
你想怎样
What you gonna do?
-来啊  -我投降不计较
- Do something. - I surrender and I let go,
我投降不计较
I surrender and I let go.
随你吧
Do that.
这上面说我们还可以
It says here we could also
烧毁整具尸体  那样也行
burn the entire body, that would work.
你到底在看什么网
What website are you on?
维基百科
Wikipedia.
什么
What?
你知道吗
Okay, you know what,
反正我们也不可能在这里点火
it's not as if we can start a fire in here anyway, so.
没错  其实不重要
Oh, yeah, actually, never mind
因为火焰温度也得高到
because it has to be hot enough
能将他烧成灰
to turn him into ash,
而不是只会给他烧的起泡泡
not just a bubbly stew person.
太棒了
That's great.
那...
So...
医院  诊所  停尸间
Hospitals, clinics, mortuaries,
他们有焚化炉
they...they have incinerators.
我妈妈  她曾经在医院工作
My mom, she used to work at a hospital,
他们也会烧掉
and they'd also discard
割下来的包皮或者胎盘之类的东西
like the old placentas and the foreskins and stuff,
他们会在晚上下夜班后烧
they burn them at the end of the night.
对对对  好吧
Right, right, right, right, right, okay.
这样也行
I can work with that.
现实世界对你来说是不是太残酷了  怪兽制造者
Is the real world too gory for you, Monster Maker?
是的
Yes.
其实还真是
Yes, it is, actually.
-你说对了  -等等
- That's the whole point. - Hold on.
殡仪馆行吗
Would a funeral home work?
胡珀街有一家
There's one on Hooper Street.
可以  太棒了
Yes, yeah, that's perfect.
我可不敢确定  多多
Uh, I don't know about that, Dot.
萝西
Rothy.
好好想想
Uh, think about it.
我们已经闯入了这个地方
We already broke into this building.
现在你们还想闯下个地方
Now you want us to break into other buildings?
去个有更多尸体的地方
There's...there's more bodies.
没错
Yes!
我们越早把这玩意送进焚化炉
The faster that we feed this fucker to the incinerator,
就能越早完事
the faster that this is done.
我们用你的信托基金
We take your trust fund money,
买机票去牙买加
we buy plane tickets to Jamaica,
喝着鸡尾酒  在沙滩上3p
and we spend the rest of our miserable year drinking mojitos
度过今年的悲惨时光
and having threesomes on the beach.
好吧
Okay, yeah.
带我们去殡仪馆
Lead us to a funeral home.
好吧
Okay, great.
清除浏览器记录
Clear your browser history,
把他搬回购物车上
put him back in the cart.
你把这里收拾干净
You, clean this shit up.
你知道我们俩
You know neither one of us
都不会参与3p的吧
is gonna be in that threesome, right?
我知道
Yeah, I know.
-快点  -好的
- Now! - Yeah, okay.
该死  该死  该死
Ah, shit, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
从这边抄近道
Come on, let's cut through here.
你能快点吗
Can you hurry up?
我真是无法理解你
I don't understand you,
但是我感觉你可能是我长久以来
but I feel like you might be the first person I've met
遇到的第一个
in a very long time...
理解我的人
that understands me.
你杀了他们后
After you kill them,
今晚过后
after tonight,
你可以教我一些东西
you can teach me some things.
我可以教你一些东西
I can teach you some things.
我们可以一起
We can be together,
就我们俩
just the two of us,
想做什么都行
doing anything we want.
没有"我们"
There is no "We."
安古斯-桑斯殡仪馆
到了
This is it.
进去吧
Let's do this.
有什么需要帮助的吗  女士
Can I help you, ma'am?
你好  是的
Um, hi, yes,
我们需要帮助
we need your help.
我们有一具尸体  有一个人
We have a dead body, and there's this guy,
她想要帮助我们
and he's trying to kill us--
请在说话前
Please press the button
按按钮  女士
before speaking, ma'am.
天啊
Oh, my God!
我们有一具尸体  有人想杀了我们
We have a dead body, someone is trying to kill us.
赶紧把门打开
Open the fucking door!
快点快点
Come, come.
那是...
Is that--
没错  没错
Yeah, yes, yes.
该死
Well, shit.
他的牙齿在哪里
Where are his goddamn teeth?
天啊  为什么所有人都要朝我们拔枪
Oh, my God, why does everyone keep pulling guns on us?
我们没时间耗了  好吗
We don't got time for this, all right?
他会杀了我们
He's gonna kill us.
谁
Who?
该死  我就知道会这样
Oh, shit, I knew that was gonna happen!
-进来  -我来了
- Get in! - I'm coming!
不  不
No. No.
No, no.
不
No!
对不起  伙计们
I'm sorry, guys.
我不行了
I can't fuckin' do this.
我不干了
I am out!
什么
What?
回来  你这个混蛋
Come back, you asshole!
杰克  操
Jack! Fuck!
好吧
Okay.
-他去哪里了  -我不知道
- Where'd he go? - I don't know.
天啊  我怎么了
God, what is my deal?
对不起  多萝西
I'm sorry, Dorothy.
对不起我把我们卷进来
I'm sorry I got us into this.
对不起  我总是惹大家烦
I'm sorry I'm always up in everyone's face,
我总是逼大家做各种事
I'm always pressuring people into doing shit.
对不起我的嘴巴永远停不下来
I'm sorry I can never stop running my fucking mouth.
冷静点  没事的
Calm down, it's fine.
你...
Um, what the--
你他妈干什么呢
what the fuck are you doing?
有人正想杀了我们呢
Somebody's trying to kill us right now.
-你  -对  不  我...
- Are you-- - Right, no, I--
滚吧  赶紧去
Fuck you. Go.
赶紧去焚化炉
Go to the incinerator please.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
等等  我找到后该干什么
Wait, what am I supposed to do once I find it?
那是个炉子  艾伦
It's an oven, Alan.
你知道怎么打开炉子吗
Do you know how to turn on an oven?
好吧
Okay.
你在哪里呢
Where the fuck are you?
操
Fuck.
祝你能进来
Good luck getting in here.
操
Fuck!
该死
Shit.
你怎么回事
What is wrong with you?
振作点
Keep it together.
你这个怂炮
You fuckin' pussy.
你可以的
You got this.
杰克
Jack!
艾伦
Alan!
说真的  你只有一块木板吗
Seriously, that's all you have?
我只找到了这个  多萝西
It was all I could find, Dorothy.
天啊  你真是把我吓了一跳
Oh, my God, you scared the shit outta me.
是这个吗  是这个吗
Is this it, this is it?
是的  加热需要一分钟
Yeah, it's gonna take a minute to heat up.
我们没有一分钟了  艾伦
We don't have a minute, Alan.
那混蛋就在楼里
The son of a bitch is in the building.
-什么  -没错
- What? - Yeah.
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
必须得加热到1000多度  不然没用的
It has to get to like 1400 degrees or it's not gonna work.
天啊
Oh, my God.
天啊  我们今晚死定了
Oh, my God, we're gonna die tonight.
我们今晚死定了
We're gonna die tonight.
我们今晚绝对要死了
We're gonna fucking die tonight.
不  好吧  别烦我
No, no, okay, don't check out on me now.
赶紧把这个搞定
Just get this thing going,
我有个主意
I have an idea.
操
Oh, fuck.
该死
Shit.
上帝啊
Please, God.
让我今晚活下来吧
Please let me live.
拜托  亲爱的小耶稣
Please, little sweet baby Jesus.
让我活下来吧
Please let me live.
我把我的钱都捐给小孩
I'll give all my money to kids.
我保证
I promise.
我会将每天都当做圣诞节般度过
I'll live my life like it's Christmas every day.
我过去  现在和未来的每一天都会好好度过
I'll live my life in the past, the present, and the future.
我不会吸毒
I will never do any drugs,
不会轻视女性
and I won't disrespect women.
拜托  亲爱的耶稣  让我活下来吧
Oh please, sweet Jesus, let me live.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
不  不
No, no!
该死
Shit.
别担心
Don't worry.
我只是来拿走尸体
I'm just gonna take the body,
然后你就能回家
and then you can go home.
对不...
I'm sor--
我很抱歉
I am so sorry,
我真的以为我可以面无表情地说出来的
I really did think I could do that with a straight face there.
那女孩在哪里
Where's the girl?
好吧
Okay.
小心点
Careful now.
你可不想不小心打歪了
You don't want to miss me
打中你的男朋友
and hit your boyfriend there.
开枪打死他
Fucking shoot him!
你抓稳他
Fucking hold him still!
操
Fuck!
赶紧找枪
Find the goddamn gun!
我够不到
I can't reach it!
我捡到了
I got it.
这就是死亡的模样  孩子
This is what death looks like, boy.
我希望那一杯酒值得
I hope that one drink was worth it.
现在死亡看上去怎么样  混蛋
How does death look now, asshole?
上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
我只要你把他带过来
I only asked you to deliver him.
你说你想确认一下
You said you wanted to make a statement.
我给你确认
There's your statement.
钱转过去了
The money is transferred.
我相信你很满意
I trust if you're satisfied
我们可以将今晚的...意外  抛诸脑后
we can put tonight's... difficulties behind us.
所有情况都处理了吗
Have all the complications been dealt with?
没有活口
No loose ends.
你听听这鬼话
You hear that BS?
手机关机了
The phone is dead.
连手机都关机了
Even the phone is dead!
我明明杀了你
I killed you.
地狱空荡荡
Hell is empty,
恶魔在人间
and all the devils are here.
我只是想拥有一点你拥有的东西
I just wanted a little bit of what you had.
但我学得很快
But I'm a fast learner.
捅我可不地道
Stabbing me wasn't very nice.
玛姬
Maggie!
但是我能告诉你一个秘密吗
But can I tell you a secret?
我很乐意摆脱各种幻想
I'm so happy to be rid of any delusions.
不  不
No, no.
装扮
Costume.
牛逼
Amazeballs.